NLRB Documents Relating to UAW Alleged Unfair Labor Practices at Caterpillar, Inc. 6266
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
NLRB Documents Relating to UAW Alleged Unfair Labor Practices at Caterpillar, Inc
1991- 2005
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
National Labor Relations Board (NLRB)
6266
0.5 cubic feet
0.5 linear ft.
Records.
6318071
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, March 07, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 07, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4232: James Gross Collection of NLRB 60th Annual Conference Files 5240: NLRB Case Files 5318: NLRB Briefs, Petitions and other Legal Documents 5355: NLRB vs. International Union of Operating Engineers Local 450 Court Documents 5435 OH: NLRB Oral History Project Miscellaneous 5740 OH: NLRB 50th Anniversary Conference Tapes and Transcripts 5843: NLRB Miscellaneous Tapes and Transcripts 5843 OHM: NLRB Oral History Project II Master Tapes 5843 OHT: NLRB Oral History Project II Transcripts 5906: NLRB Additional Case Files relating to Health Care 6122m: NLRB "Hebrew Free Burial Association, Case AO-279" Papers 6171: NLRB Decisions by Stipulation: Classified Index of National Labor Relations Board Decisions and Related Court Decisions (DS Reports)
Unfair labor practices--Cases.; Agricultural laborers--Labor unions.; Caterpillar Inc.; International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America.; United States. National Labor Relations Board.
6318071
- Peoria Journal Star. "$3.4 Billion in Exports Means 18,500 U.S. Jobs at Cat.", 1991 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Feb. 17th. Peoria, IL.
- Caterpillar. "We're Not Just a Tractor Company Anymore.", 1991 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Sept. 10th.
- "Question Pattern Bargaining." Decatur, IL., 1992 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  March 25th. Herald & Review.
- Caterpillar., 1992 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  March 31st. Correspondence.
- Caterpillar., 1992 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Aug. 27th. Statement.
- Caterpillar., 1992 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Oct. 16th. Correspondence #2.
- Caterpillar. "Why?", 2005 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Jun.14th.
- Caterpillar. "Matter of Fact.", 1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Feb. 15th.
- Caterpillar. "Matter of Fact.", 1993 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  March 12th.
- Exhibit 565. Chronology-Draft., 1994 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  April.
- NLRB. Decision., 1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Nov. 23rd.
- NLRB. Decision., 1995 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Jan. 5th.
- NLRB. Decision., 1995 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Jan. 31.
- Expert Opinion of Dr. Peter J. Carnevale. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  . Exhibit 446.
- Supplement to the Expert Opinion of Dr. Peter J. Carnevale., 1995 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Feb. 27th. Exhibit 448.
- NLRB., 1995 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  May 18th. Order Transferring Proceedings to the NLRB.
- Peoria Journal Star. "Shootings Stun Cat and UAW.", 1995 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  Sept. 1st. Peoria, IL.
- Central Agreement Proposal No.6., 1995 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  Nov. 28th.
- Daily Times. "Unfair Labor Strike Called Off.", 1995 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  Dec. 4th. Decatur, IL.